so let's go over how you can use
所以让我们来看看你是如何使用
inkscape to replace every instance of a
Inkscape来替换
single color on a document all at once
文档上一次只有一种颜色
if you see from my example design here I
如果您从我的示例设计中看到，我
have this assortment of objects in a
将这些分类的对象放在一个
variety of colors let's say I want to
各种颜色，比方说我想
take every object with this salmon color
把所有这种鲑鱼色的东西都拿出来
right here and change it to a yellow
就在这里，把它改成黄色
shade normally to do that I would have
正常遮阳来做我会做的
to click on each object individually and
要单独单击每个对象并
change the colors one by one which can
逐个更改颜色，这样可以
be a pretty tedious and time-consuming
是一个相当乏味和耗时的
task depending on the size of your
任务取决于您的
artwork
艺术品
there is an easier way to go about doing
做某事有一种更容易的方法
this in inkscape though in order to do
在Inkscape中这样做是为了
this what I'm going to first do is I'm
这是我要做的第一件事
going to click on one object right here
点击此处的一个对象
that contains the color that I'd like to
那里面有我想要的颜色
change with the object selected I'm
更改选定的对象我是
going to come up to the edit menu I'll
转到编辑菜单，我将
go down to select same and in this menu
向下选择相同并在此菜单中
over here to the right you should see
在这里的右边，你应该会看到
all of these different attributes that
所有这些不同的属性
you can choose to select your objects by
您可以选择通过以下方式选择对象
so for example if I choose to select my
例如，如果我选择选择我的
objects by fill color
按填充颜色显示的对象
it's going to select every single object
它将选择每个单独的对象
on my document that contains that fill
在我的包含该填充的文档上
color of the one object I have selected
我选择的一个对象的颜色
and to change that color now all I have
为了改变我现在所拥有的颜色
to do is apply a different shade like
要做的是应用一种不同的色调，如
that and as you can see every single
正如你所看到的，每一个
color has been replaced with the color
颜色已被替换为
that I chose there now this example here
我在这里选择了这个例子
contains several colors so I'll have to
包含几种颜色，所以我必须
repeat this process a couple of more
再重复这个过程几次
times I'm going to select this object up
乘以我要选择这个对象的次数
here I'll go to edit select same and if
在这里，我将转到编辑，选择相同的，如果
you look over here you can see all of
你看这里，你可以看到所有的
these different properties that you can
这些不同的属性可以
use to select your objects by you could
使用可通过以下方式选择您的对象
select by fill and stroke not just the
按填充和描边选择，而不仅仅是
fill you can select by just the fill
填充您可以仅按填充进行选择
color just the stroke color just the
颜色只是笔触的颜色只是
stroke style and by object type whether
笔划样式以及是否按对象类型
it be a square or a circle or even a
它是一个正方形或圆形，甚至是一个
custom drawn path with the bezier pen
使用Bezier钢笔自定义绘制路径
I'm just going to use fill color for
我将使用填充色
this demonstration and I'm going to
这个演示和我要做的
change that to a lighter shade of yellow
把它改成淡黄色。
and then I'll change this color of this
然后我要把这个换成这个颜色
object right here I'll go to edit select
对象就在这里，我将转到编辑选择
same
相同
fill color
填充颜色
and I'll change this to a darker shade
我会把这个换成深色的
of yellow maybe something a little off
黄色的，也许有点不对劲
like orange add a little orange in there
像橙色一样，在里面加一点橙色
okay that looks good
好的，看起来不错。
and now we are finished as you can see
现在我们完成了，正如你所看到的
it's as simple as changing colors
它就像换颜色一样简单
globally on your document is as simple
对您的文档进行全局操作非常简单
as selecting the one object that
作为选择一个对象，
contains that color and then using the
包含该颜色，然后使用
edit menu to select every other object
编辑菜单以选择所有其他对象
so that is how you can go about
这就是你如何行动的方式
performing a color replace using
使用执行颜色替换
inkscape if you found this lesson useful
Inkscape如果你觉得这一课有用
then consider checking out my inkscape
那就考虑看看我的Inkscape吧
master class it's a collection of over
大师类，它是一个集合
60 videos where I go over all of the
60个视频，我浏览了所有
tools and features in inkscape and I
Inkscape和I中的工具和功能
explain what they are and demonstrate
解释它们是什么并演示它们
how they work kind of like how I did in
它们的工作原理有点像我在
this video we even have a private
这个视频我们甚至有一个私人的
Community where you can ask questions
您可以提出问题的社区
and get help from me anytime you want
只要你愿意，随时向我寻求帮助
and best of all there's no monthly
最棒的是没有月刊
membership fees you just pay 17 one time
会员费你只需一次性付17英镑
and you're in for Life I'll have some
你要终身监禁，我要喝一些
information about that down below if you
下面是关于这方面的信息，如果你
want to check that out as always thanks
我想一如既往地检查一下，谢谢
for watching
观看
foreign
国外
[Music]
[音乐]